歡笑之聲遍世間，
Jollity, forever shown;
樂道之者卻鮮見。
path of joy, so few have known.
那份真實的誠摯，
Sincerity and emphasis,
僅在歡樂中看見。
so truly seen in happiness.
人的心靈，可以苟且，可以突出
With one mind, we can make, we can live
人的生命，可以接受，可以付出
With a life, one can take, one can give
我們歡笑，分享著我們的一切
We rejoice, lending all we possess
人的聲音，可以如塵，可以如鐘
With a voice, one can lift or depress
歡笑之聲遍世間，
Jollity, forever shown;
樂道之者卻鮮見。
path of joy, so few have known.
那份真實的誠摯，
Sincerity and emphasis,
僅在歡樂中看見。
so truly seen in happiness.
在歡笑中
In happiness
這場大夢不允許一點怨氣
In this dream, there is no room for spite
但卻好像是我自己的決定
Still it seems, only I can decide
我迷了路，但卻不用待在世間
I am lost, but am free of the world
在我眼裡，那是冰冷，那是蒼涼
For outside, all is bleak, all is cold
歡笑之聲遍世間，
Jollity, forever shown;
樂道之者卻鮮見。
path of joy, so few have known.
那份真實的誠摯，
Sincerity and emphasis,
僅在歡樂中看見。
so truly seen in happiness.
歡笑之聲遍世間，
Jollity, forever shown;
樂道之者卻鮮見。
path of joy, so few have known.
那份真實的誠摯，
Sincerity and emphasis,
僅在歡樂中看見。
so truly seen in happiness.
在歡笑中
In happiness